let's have a look at the rectangle tool
让我们来看看矩形工具
I select it now I drag over the body of
我选择它，现在我将它拖到
the crocodile as with the ellipse tool I
鳄鱼就像椭圆工具一样
can drag the two squares and when I drag
可以拖动两个正方形，当我拖动时
the circle all four corners get rounded
所有四个角的圆都变圆了
I want however only to round two corners
不过，我只想绕过两个弯。
I click on the make Corner sharp again
我再次点击Make Corner Sharp
icon to round individual Corners I click
我点击的圆角图标
on the Node tool I click on ADD Corners
在Node工具上，单击Add Corners
now I can adjust Each corner
现在我可以调整每个角落
individually to create a curve at the
单独创建一条曲线
bottom left corner I drag the small
我拖着左下角的小
circle up
向上圈
I get two arrows showing the start and
我得到了两个箭头，显示了开始和
end points of the curve I drag the arrow
曲线的终点我拖动箭头
all the way up and around the bottom
一路向上，绕过底部
right corner I drag the circle to the
在右角，我将圆圈拖到
left I don't want to border so I shift
左转我不想边界，所以我改变了方向
click on the Red Cross
点击红十字会
in the layers panel I can see I placed a
在层面板中，我可以看到我放置了一个
rectangle I will name the rectangle body
矩形我会将矩形主体命名为
because the rectangle was created last
因为该矩形是最后创建的
it lies above the other elements so I
它位于其他元素之上，所以我
want to lower the body when I click on
当我点击的时候我想把身体放低
the down arrow I am lowering the body
向下的箭头我要放下身体
but when there are many objects it is
但当有许多物体时，它就是
faster to drag it to another place
更快地将其拖到另一个地方
notice I could even add it to a group
请注意，我甚至可以将其添加到组中
when I drag and hold it above a group
当我将其拖动并按住在组上方时
the group opens and I can place it where
该组将打开，我可以将其放置在
I want I will press Ctrl set to undo and
我想我会按Ctrl Set来撤消，然后
close the group with the select tool
使用选择工具关闭组
selected you can click on the raise and
选中后，您可以单击加薪和
lower icons which do the same as the up
与Up相同的下部图标
and down arrows and with the raise to
和向下的箭头，随着上升到
top and lower to bottom icons you can
顶部图标和从下到下图标
quickly place an item to the top or the
快速将项目放到顶部或
bottom of a layer
层的底部
now let's make the feet I click on the
现在让我们把脚放在我点击的
rectangle tool and drag over a foot to
矩形工具并将其拖到脚上以
quickly go to the select tool press the
快速转到选择工具，按下
space bar now I can adjust from every
空格键现在我可以从每一个
corner and to return to the rectangle
角点并返回到矩形
tool press the space bar again
工具再次按空格键
I drag the circle to round the corners I
我拖着圆圈绕过角落
see the top corners are a bit different
看，上面的角有点不同
so I click on the Node tool I click on
所以我点击了我所点击的节点工具
ADD Corners to adjust the curve I drag
添加拐角以调整我拖动的曲线
the left Circle up and at the right I
左边向上圈，右边我
drag the smaller Circle down
将较小的圆圈向下拖
I press the space bar to go to the
我按空白键转到
select tool
选择工具
now I duplicate the foot and drag it to
现在我复制脚并将其拖到
the other foot I click on the brown
另一只脚我点击棕色
Swatch that I pinned in the swatches
我钉在样本中的样本
panel to place the foot behind the other
将脚放在另一只脚后面的面板
foot I click on the lower icon
脚我点击下面的图标
I shift-click on the other foot right
我向右移动-点击另一只脚
click and choose group then I click on
单击并选择群组，然后我单击
the lower to bottom icon in the layers
层中从下到下的图标
panel I will call the group left feet
小组我将称之为左脚小组
I right click on the group and choose
我右键单击群组并选择
duplicate I click on Lower to bottom in
重复我点击从低到低
the layers panel I call the group right
我称之为正确的层面板
feet I drag the feet and when I hold
脚我拖着脚，当我握住时
Ctrl while dragging I can drag in a
拖动时按住我可以拖动
straight line I can do this horizontally
直线我可以水平地做到
and vertically
和垂直
in the next lecture we will create the
在下一堂课中，我们将创建
scutes using the pencil tool
使用铅笔工具进行羽毛板